<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="main_items_array">
        <item>How SahiCareer can help you in your Career</item>
        <item>SahiCareer\'s Career Assessment Test</item>
        <item>SahiCareer\'s Career Guidance</item>
        <item>SahiCareer mentorship</item>
        <item>What is the best part in career explorer from SahiCareer?</item>
        <item>SahiCareer Resume Builder</item>
        <item>Why does a School need SahiCareer?</item>
        <item>Why does a College need SahiCareer?</item>
        <item>How is SahiCareer better over competition?</item>
        <item>Other questions</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_a">
        <item>How can SahiCareer help me plan my career?</item>
        <item>How is SahiCareer different from others?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_b">
        <item>What makes you different from other career \nassessment tests?</item>
        <item>How reliable is the career assessment test?</item>
        <item>What if I start the assessment test but can\'t
            \ncontinue.Can I complete the test some other time?</item>
        <item>What is the difference between the Free
            \nassessment report and Paid assessment report?</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_c">
        <item>What is the background of the SahiCareer career \ncounsellors?</item>
        <item>Why do I need a career counsellor?</item>
        <item>How can a career counsellor guide me to choose \nthe right job?</item>
        <item>My family and friends have advised me a career \ndifferent from that in my report. What should I do?</item>
        <item>What modes of counselling do you offer?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_d">
        <item>How do you ensure that I find a mentor matching \nmy profile?</item>
        <item>What is the background of the SahiCareer career \nmentors?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_e">
        <item>What is SahiCareer\'s career explorer?</item>
        <item>Why career exploration is important?</item>
        <item>Does SahiCareer\'s career explorer tell me my \nperfect career?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_f">
        <item>How does your Resume Generator work?</item>
        <item>How does resume play a role in getting a job?</item>
        <item>What is the fees for building my resume?</item>
        <item>I am not happy with my resume. Can I get some \nhelp?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_g">
        <item>How will our school benefit from your Career \nGuidance System?</item>
        <item>We already have a Career Counsellor in our school.\nWhy do we need SahiCareer?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_h">
        <item>How will our college benefit from the SahiCareer \nCareer Guidance?</item>
        <item>We already have a Career Counsellor in our college.\nWhy do we need SahiCareer?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_i">
        <item>What different services does SahiCareer offer?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_array_j">
        <item>Does SahiCareer guarantee Data Confidentiality?</item>
        <item>Are parents involved in this Guidance Process?</item>
        <item>Do you have any commercial partner?</item>
        <item>Are the tests online or paper-based?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sub_one_items_arrray_default">
        <item>Nothing to display</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="desc_a_one">
        <item>A career starts with knowing about the perfect
            \nindustry,qualification and job for you.
            \nSahiCareer will help you realise your passion,
            \ninterests, and abilities and facilitate your
            \ncareer goals through a concrete career plan.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_a_two">
        <item>SahiCareer is different and better on multiple
            \ncounts.
            \nFirstly, our career test is the most scientific and
            \nwell researched test, with the highest accuracy and
            \nreliability.
            \nSecondly, all career counsellors possess deep
            \nknowledge,have a psychology or MSW background,
            \nand are trained to counsel youth in the best
            \npossible way.
            \nThirdly, we go further in helping you with your
            \ndream career by providing you with additional
            \ncareer services,resume builder,resume services,
            \nschool and college information.
            \nAll of this to help you in your career!
            \nFourth,we have highly established industry mentors
            \nfrom different industries and with strong experience
            \nto personally mentor the SahiCareer youth.?</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_b_one">
        <item>Our career assessment test is the most reliable and
            \naccurate test. Most tests either test aptitude
            \nor interest.
            \nSahiCareer\'s test is multi-faceted and tests aptitude,
            \ninterest, personality and work style!
            \nIt has been designed after extensive research with
            \nyouth, and suggests the best possible careers.
            \nOur test can also be customised in multiple
            \nlanguages and for different industries.
            \nWe are also continually updating and improving our
            \ntest through ongoing research.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_b_two">
        <item>Our test has proven to be highly reliable with youth.
            \nThe test uses the best in class research framework
            \nand has the unique ability to comprehensively
            \nanalyse an individual\'s best career possibilities</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_b_three">
        <item>Yes, you can continue your assessment test at your
            \nconvenience. However, we believe that it is best to
            \nfinish the test in one sitting.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_b_four">
        <item>Free assessment will give you the basic career
            \nresults.While a free test is useful for your career,
            \nthe paid career assessment test will help you with
            \nmany additional things.
            \nThe paid assessment report will give you details
            \nabout your
            \n1) Interests
            \n2) Abilities
            \n3) Personality
            \n4) Workstyle
            \nIn addition to this, the detailed assessment report
            \nwill get into the details of each career and all
            \npotential career paths that you are suitable for you.
            \nThis detailed career report can work as a great
            \nguide for you whenever you are looking to make
            \ncareer decisions, now or in the future.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="desc_c_one">
        <item>We have highly experienced counsellor who have
            \nextensive experience in working with you,
            \nand who will help you in exploring and
            \nunderstanding your best career.
            \nAll SahiCareer counsellors have a psychology
            \nor MSW background.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_c_two">
        <item>Our career counsellor will help you develop a
            \nbroader understanding of your own self and about
            \nwork and education, further helping you make
            \ninformed educational, career and life decisions.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_c_three">
        <item>Our career counsellors work with individuals at
            \nvarious stages in their careers. They will help
            \nyou determine what careers you are best suited
            \nfor given your interests, personality, abilities
            \nand work style. Our counsellor will develop your
            \ncareer plan to improve your current career and
            \nprovide advice about entering a new profession.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_c_four">
        <item>Family and friends are our well-wishers.
            \nIt is always good to get an external opinion also,
            \nfrom career experts. You will always have the
            \nchoice to determine your own career, after all.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_c_five">
        <item>We provide three modes counselling: Face to Face,
            \nVideo and Telephonic counselling.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_d_one">
        <item>We have experienced industry mentors to
            \npersonally guide.
            \nWe help you find the right mentor by matching you
            \nwith a mentor who is from a similar industry,
            \neducational background and location.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_d_two">
        <item>Our mentors are successful professionals, are
            \narmed with diverse industry experience, are
            \nhelpful and are extremely keen to facilitate
            \nthe youth towards their best careers!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_e_one">
        <item>Our career explorer is a convenient, easy to use,
            \nonline resource that provides instructive,
            \ninsightful information that can empower you to
            \ntake control of your career exploration journey
            \nin few easy steps.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_e_two">
        <item>In making career decisions, the work you choose
            \nto pursue will have a direct impact on the way
            \nyou live your life. Good career planning and
            \ndecision-making involves learning about careers,
            \ntypes of work, educational requirements, and job
            \nfunctions. These are critically important in
            \nunderstanding which careers meet your interests
            \nand goals.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_e_three">
        <item>Our career explorer can\'t tell you your perfect job.
            \nIt does however allow you to match your personal
            \nattitudes and behaviours to the careers database
            \nso you can explore potential careers and understand
            \nthem more.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_f_one">
        <item>Our resume generator works automatically.
            \nYou simply enter in data, and you get the output.
            \nThe output is the resume which is professional
            \nand elegant. At each stage of Building the resume,
            \nwe will guide you and give examples. Besides that,
            \nwe have several experts from different industry
            \nwho will give you tips make your resume more
            \nattractive and professional.
            </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_f_two">
        <item>Resume is the back bone of your job application
            \nand plays a very important role in influencing
            \nthe recruiter hire/ interview you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_f_three">
        <item>Our online resume builder gives is absolutely free!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_f_four">
        <item>Yes, we understand it\'s not easy to build a great
            \nresume.Which is why we have a team of experts
            \nwho analyse your resume, consult you and prepare
            \na revised,professional and highly impactful resume?
            </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_g_one">
        <item>The students have a long term career plan
            \nprepared for them. They become self-aware
            \nand goal-oriented from an early age.
            \nThe students also have an external voice
            \nto share their thoughts, beliefs and opinions.
            \nThe students benefit immensely, which results in
            \nmassive benefit for the school. The college has a
            \nstrong marketing tool to attract future students,
            \nbuilds stronger credibility, and has a stronger,
            \nmore engaged and successful alumni.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_g_two">
        <item>Our long term student guidance plan keeps the
            \nstudent\'s career well-being in focus at all times.
            \nWe track a student?s progress, report to the
            \nmanagement, and plan interventions if required.
            \n\nWe also involve parents and the school
            \nmanagementin decision-making, since they are
            \nthe key influencers for the children.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_h_one">
        <item>College is a critical time for the students careers.
            \nThe students have a long term career plan
            \nprepared for them.
            \nThey become self-aware and goal-oriented
            \nfrom an early age. The students also have an
            \nexternal voice to share their thoughts, beliefs and
            \nopinions.
            \nThe students benefit immensely, which results in
            \nmassive benefit for the college. The college has a
            \nstrong marketing tool to attract future students,
            \nbuilds stronger credibility, and has a stronger,
            \nmore engaged and successful alumni.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_h_two">
        <item>Our long term student guidance plan keeps the
            \nstudent\'s career well-being in focus at all times.
            \nWe track a student\'s progress, report to the
            \nmanagement, and plan interventions if required.
            \nWe also involve parents and the school
            \nmanagement in decision-making, since they are
            \nthe key influencers for the children.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_i_one">
        <item>SahiCareer has the following services which are the
            \nbest for career guidance: Most scientific and
            \naccurate career assessment test Highly skilled
            \ncounsellors,with prior experience of counselling
            \nyouth Strong mentorship system, with a solid base
            \nof industry professionals Allied services on the
            \nportal ?resume services, institutional data,
            \ncareer blogs</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="desc_j_one">
        <item>SahiCareer guarantees data confidentially.
            \nWe believe data is of utmost important, and will
            \nsign a non-disclosure agreement with you.
            \nAll data will be kept securely, and safely.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_j_two">
        <item>Yes, parents are involved. Since parents are critical
            \ninfluencers in the career planning process of their
            \nchildren,we invite parents to be a part of
            \ncounselling, and also share their child\'s progress
            \nwith them.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_j_three">
        <item>No. Apart from schools, colleges and individuals,
            \nwe do not have any other commercial partners.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc_j_four">
        <item>The tests are completely online, and compatible
            \nwith any device or browser.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Skill_Experience">
        <item>Beginner</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Advanced</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Language_proficiency">
        <item>Beginner</item>
        <item>Intermediate</item>
        <item>Advanced</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>